I'm in the Seal Show.
Today's big up goes to Shantae Broadus,
wife of Snoop Dogg for laying down the law.
The hip-hop legend from the West Side
was recently talking about OnlyFans.
He claimed he turned down an offer from the site
that could have netted him as much as a hundred mil
to pull that thing out, y'all.
He said straight up, I got a black wife.
Ain't no way in the world she gonna allow me
to go in there and pull that thing out
for no amount of money.
Because you know if he was married to Kris Jenner,
she would have been like, bring him out!
She would have played T.I.
Bring him out, bring him out!
Today's letdown goes to bricks of color
for taking a rap for something they didn't do.
Okay, do y'all remember this?
I know y'all remember this.
A woman in Houston had come on the internet.
She said she was attacked in the face with a brick.
She said she was coming out the club.
She had the whole knot on her face.
And she was like, these cats,
this man knocked me in my head with a brick.
You know, because I said that I wasn't gonna
give him my phone number
and y'all ain't do nothing.
Y'all ain't do nothing.
Y'all, she was lying.
Bruh, she is on the run.
This was all a scammy am.
And she raised $42,000 on GoFundMe.
She turned it up and said it was a brick
and it had to be a brick of color.
It was a black, it was a red brick.
Black brick.
Like, white bricks are not getting wrongfully blamed, y'all.
All bad.
Nobody is, nobody is blaming white bricks.
We are.